[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "RBR", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "What do you --what do you read into that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "Well, I mean, you said his speech was a little more reasonable this year.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 60, "question": "Does the president of Iran really have much power?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 61, "answer": "Well, that really depends on the situation.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iran"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Israel", "Israel", "U.S."]}, "docId": "120926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NN", "NNP", "VBZ", ":", "CC", "IN", "JJS", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 67, "question": "Does it depend on who wins the election?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 68, "answer": "Well, I think one thing Israel is -- or at least some people in Israel are trying to do is to push the U.S. to kind of do it for them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBP", "IN", "VBD", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 78, "question": "Were you surprised or dismayed or both by Barack Obama refusing to sit down with any world leaders this week?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "VBN", "CC", "DT", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 79, "answer": "You know, I was -- I did think that was missed opportunity.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "WRB", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 99, "question": "Should America's intervention now be reigned back or is this a time to really get more involved?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "CC", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "JJR", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 100, "answer": "Well, we were in a sense playing a public master role in the past when dictators were there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", ":", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 118, "question": "What more can it be doing in places like Cambodia to tackle this kind of thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "JJR", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 119, "answer": "RISTOF: Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Cambodia"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 159, "question": "So the obvious question for you is 41 day to go, who is going to win?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 160, "answer": "Sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Quinnipiac Polls"], "PERCENT": ["53 percent"], "PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "120926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "VBN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 173, "question": "What is the reality of their value?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 174, "answer": "Right now Obama in these Quinnipiac Polls is at 53 percent in each of these states, which means it's not good enough anymore for Romney to pick up the undecided voters.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["47 percent"]}, "docId": "120926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NNS", "VBD", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "WP", "NNS", "CD", "VBZ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CC", "VB", "TO", ":", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 186, "question": "What would you recommend him to do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 187, "answer": "Well, you know, I think what the 47 percent comments revealed is that he wasn't doing what politics 101 says you should do and play to -- play to the center.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 193, "question": "Would he have done better having someone like Marco Rubio, for example?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "RBR", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 194, "answer": "Sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marco Rubio"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Saudi Arabia"]}, "docId": "120926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "POS", "NNS", "RB", "RB", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 237, "question": "How important is it to you to be doing this in Saudi Arabia?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "TO", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 238, "answer": "I think women's rights not only are, like you said, at the vanguard of what we really need to focus on in Saudi Arabia but also in the region.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Saudi Arabia"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 253, "question": "What is your overview at the moment of where we -- where we are and is war likely or more common sense prevailed, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "VBZ", "NN", "JJ", "CC", "JJR", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 254, "answer": "Well, I believe common sense will prevail but I think it's going to be a tough slog.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 275, "question": "What can America or what should America do if anything to hasten or to change the current process?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "NNP", "CC", "WP", "MD", "NNP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 276, "answer": "It should inspire hope, trust, stability and compassion.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America", "America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 299, "question": "But what is the ethos that leaders and countries need to adopt to try and stop this horrible cycle now of a youth who just feel disenfranchise and not able to fulfill their potential?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 300, "answer": "Economic development.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 353, "question": "Why are the Danes so healthy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 354, "answer": "Because they have social security.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBZ", "CC", "NNS", "CC", "VBD", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 376, "question": "Why is the rest of the world overtaking and what should be done about it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "CC", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "I think it is really priorities and values and greed, really.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "General, you're itching to get in?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "I want to pitch in on manufacturing for a second.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "Or should it be a global trading partner to mutual benefit?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "VBG", "NN", "TO", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "I think that we live in a very diverse world and we need to embrace that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "Who says 50 percent of the world is living on less than two dollars a day, 20 percent less than one dollar a day?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "JJR", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "DT", "NN", ",", "CD", "NN", "RBR", "IN", "CD", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "I travel the planet.", "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["two dollars"], "PERCENT": ["50 percent", "20 percent"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "Why is the CGI now so important to so many people in your position?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "Because of what you are seeing in front of you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 517, "question": "Foaming at the mouth as usual?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 518, "answer": "Now it's really wonderful now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 574, "question": "Was it a touchdown?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 575, "answer": "I don't think it was a touchdown.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120926pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP$", ":", "DT", "CD", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 581, "question": "Are you falling for him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 582, "answer": "No, I'm not falling for him, but I do think maybe his -- the one who is giving him his meds has finally found the right balance.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]